(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください...
Please wait a moment until the performance begins...
ヤマトファンタジア
Yamato Phantasia
出演：白上フブキ / 百鬼あやめ / 大神ミオ / さくらみこ
Cast: Shirakami Fubuki / Nakiri Ayame / Ookami Mio / Sakura Miko
#ヤマトファンタジア
#YamatoPhantasia
ピンポンパンポーン！
Ding-dong-dang-dong!
皆様 大変長らくお待たせいたしました。
Everyone, thank you for waiting so long.
まもなく ライブ開演となります！
The live concert will begin shortly!
最後に注意事項の確認だよ！
Let's check the rules one last time!
およ？
Oh?
今回のライブはスクリーンショットや...
For this live concert, you can take screenshots and...
音声なしの30秒までの動画なら SNSに投稿してOK！
post videos up to 30 seconds without audio on SNS!
おおー！
Ooh!
なので どんどん皆 投稿してください！
So everyone, please post as much as you like!
すごい！ はーい！
Amazing! Okay!
感想もハッシュタグ ヤマトファンタジア で...
And for your thoughts, use the hashtag #YamatoPhantasia...
たくさんツイートしてね 皆！
and tweet a lot, everyone!
ヤマトファンタジアだよ！
It's #YamatoPhantasia!
ファンタジア！
Phantasia!
よろしくお願いいたします！
We appreciate your support!
皆 ライブ楽しんでいきましょう！
Everyone, let's enjoy the live concert!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ホロライトブレードとか 花火もどんどん使って盛り上げてね！
You can use Hololight Blades and fireworks too, so use them to hype things up!
もちろん！
Of course!
ニェー！
Nye!
ストリーミングプラスの皆もコメントで盛り上げてね！
Everyone on Streaming+, use the comments to hype things up!
盛り上げてね！
Hype it up!
お願いね 皆！
We're counting on you, everyone!
ありがとう 待っててくれてありがとう！
Thank you, thank you for waiting!
それじゃあ 皆 準備はいいかな？
Now then, is everyone ready?
プロトライブ セカンド ヤマトファンタジア...
Protolive #2 Yamato Phantasia...
せーの！
Ready...
始まりだー！
Go!
イェーイ！
Yay!
うおおおおおお
Uoooooo
Everything's gonna be alright
感じよう 今 磐座で Be with you
Let's feel it now at the Iwakura, be with you
KONKON Beats ヤマトファンタジア ver.
KONKON Beats (Yamato Phantasia ver.)
目覚めろ 魂！
Awaken, soul!
ヤマトファンタジア 始まるよー！
Yamato Phantasia is starting!
盛り上がって いくぞー！
Let's get hyped!
フブちゃん
Fubuki-chan
こんこんきーつね
Kon-kon kitsune
こんばんみぉーん！
Good evening-miooon!
リズム 太陽におはようしていたり
Starting the day with the rhythm of the sun,
真昼の月におやすみしていたり
or saying goodnight to the midday moon
いつだって僕らはちょっとズレている
We're always a little out of sync,
丸い地球のせいかもね Ah
maybe it's because the Earth is round. Ah,
ひとごとみたいじゃん？ 時々キツネらしい
it sounds like someone else's business? Sometimes it feels like being a fox
そこんとこ よろしくね
So please bear with me.
世界中が待ってて
The whole world is waiting,
夢じゃないってことが 今から本当になる
and the fact that it's not a dream is about to become reality
Are you ready?
こんこんコン コンな狐に化かされて
Kon-kon-kon, bewitched by this kind of fox,
ドクドクドク 心をアゲて
doku-doku-doku, lift your heart
Everything's gonna be alright 感じよう 今 磐座で Be with you
Everything's gonna be alright, let's feel it now at the Iwakura, be with you
はい 嫌なことがあった日でも
Yes, even on days when bad things happen,
笑えちゃう僕らがいいね
it's great that we can still laugh.
そうだ君がフレンドなら無敵じゃない？ってことよ
That's right, if you're my friend, aren't we invincible?
今でも本気にしてる
I still believe that in earnest.
生まれも育ちも 話す言葉も
Our birthplace, our upbringing, the words we speak,
趣味も歩幅も ひとつの愛し方も
our hobbies, our pace, and the way we love,
いつだって僕らはちょっとズレている
we're always slightly different from each other.
それを大事にしてよ
Please cherish that.
Are you ready? コンコンコン
Are you ready? Kon kon kon!
イエス こんなキツネに化かされて
Yes! I'm a fox who's bewitched you!
Love Love Love 心をあげて
Love Love Love, give me your heart!
Yeah Yeah Everything's gonna be alright
感情今 うわさの Feel with you
Emotions now, that rumored 'Feel with you'.
もう一回 コンコンコン
One more time! Kon kon kon!
イエス こんなキツネに化かされて
Yes! I'm a fox who's bewitched you!
Love Love Love 心をあげて
Love Love Love, give me your heart!
Yeah Yeah Top music
ほら後まで行くよ
Look, it'll reach even the back!
今 空の波にチューニング
Now, tuning into the waves of the sky...
Wow Wow コンコンコン 魔法をかけて
Wow Wow Kon kon kon! Cast a spell!
上を向けるまで Feel with you
Until you can look up, Feel with you!
最高！
Awesome!
ハイ！ ハイ！
Hai! Hai!
皆さんありがとうございました！
Thank you very much, everyone!
まだまだ最後まで楽しんでいってくださいね！
Please continue to enjoy yourselves until the very end!
愛してるぜー！
I love you all!
放て この思いを 鮮やかに
Release these feelings vividly,
響け 乙女の歌
echo forth, the maiden's song!
乙女のすすめ！
Otome no Susume!
にゃっはろー！
Nyaho-hello!
エリート巫女の、さくらみこだにぇー！
It's the elite miko, Sakura Miko!
みんな、盛り上がっていくぞー！
Everyone, let's get hyped up!
前向いてぐんぐん出発進行
Looking forward, moving right along, full speed ahead!
立ち止まる予定あるわけない
I have no intention of stopping!
笑顔にさせちゃう神様進行
A divine advance that'll make everyone smile!
それつまりどこのどなた様？
And just who exactly might that be?
じゃあ始めようか 空を染め上げて
Well then, shall we begin? Dyeing the sky with color...
ほらあっちもこっちもそっちもどっちも
Look, over here, over there, everywhere you look!
日進月歩 華やかに
Steady progress, made in spectacular fashion!
変えていこうよ
Let's keep on changing!
桜ひらり 咲き誇り
Cherry blossoms fluttering, in full bloom,
甘酸っぱくなれるように
so that they can become bittersweet.
一歩 右に左 輝く姿
Moving left and right, a sparkling figure,
信じてついてきてね
believe in me and follow along!
桜ひらり 夢を見たり
Cherry blossoms fluttering, dreaming dreams,
どんな困難だって
no matter what difficulties arise,
きっと 君と二人乗り越えるよ
I'm sure the two of us can overcome them together.
上手歌うよ さあすすめ
I'll sing my heart out, now let's go!
ピアッサンサン 登る太陽
Piyassan-san, the rising sun!
春の光 すすはれの空
Spring light, in a clear and bright sky!
上手のフリして ここにいたいな
I want to stay right here, pretending to be skillful!
君に届けたいこの思い
These feelings I want to convey to you...
さあ悩み隠る 人は聞きなさい
Now, for those hiding their worries, listen closely!
そういっぱいいっぱいあるのより
Instead of having many, many things,
いっぱい絶対幸せを
let's find absolute happiness,
知れば大吉
and if you know it, you'll have great luck!
桜ひらり 咲き誇り
Cherry blossoms fluttering, in full bloom,
甘酸っぱい気持ち
a bittersweet feeling...
ずっと胸に胸に持ち続けて
I'll keep it in my heart forever and ever,
願いを叶えていくよ
and make my wishes come true!
桜ひらり 夢を見たり
Cherry blossoms fluttering, dreaming dreams,
憧れた景色がある
there's a scenery I've longed for.
ずっと 君の隣 掴めるから
By your side, I can reach out and grab it,
光を添えて いざすすめ
adding light to the path, now let's go!
上手歌うよ さあすすめ
I'll sing my heart out, now let's go!
かじかむ冬に勝った人に
To those who've overcome the freezing winter,
枝の先 膨らんでいる蕾
the buds at the ends of the branches are swelling.
春の風を待ってたんだよ
They've been waiting for the spring breeze...
それは君という風
and that breeze is you!
背中を押す 進行は
An advance that pushes us forward!
桜ひらり 咲き誇り
Cherry blossoms fluttering, in full bloom,
甘酸っぱくなれるように
so that they can become bittersweet.
一歩 右に左 輝く姿
Moving left and right, a sparkling figure,
信じてついてきてね
believe in me and follow along!
桜ひらり 夢を見たり
Cherry blossoms fluttering, dreaming dreams,
どんな困難だって
no matter what difficulties arise,
きっと 君と二人乗り越えるよ
I'm sure the two of us can overcome them together.
上手歌うよ さあすすめ
I'll sing my heart out, now let's go!
夢花火
Dream Fireworks
作詞・作曲 Halo 編曲 葛目将之
Lyrics/Music: Halo, Arrangement: Masayuki Kuzume
鈴の音響く 深い夜と お月様
The bells ring out through the deep night and the moon
今宵 宴の用意を
Prepare for tonight's banquet
高笑い堪え ああ 式神を連れ立って
Suppressing a loud laugh, ah, with the Shikigami in tow
戯れに興じるの
Engaging in playfulness
流れゆく時を想う
Thinking of the passing time
消えゆく日々ならば
If they are days that fade away
この切なさも美しよ
Even this sadness is beautiful
響かせて そら高く
Let it ring out, high into the sky
そっと はんなりはんなり 夢花火
Softly, elegantly, elegant dream fireworks
ふんわりふんわり 願うのは
Gently, gently, what I wish for is
…消えたから
...since it disappeared,
君に会って気付く
meeting you, I realized
もう一人じゃない
that I'm not alone anymore.
さあ行こう
Come on, let's go,
瞬きを越え　駆け月　響く
beyond the blink of an eye, the running moon resonates,
爪弾く道　金泥の群　共に嘆く夜
the plucked road, the group of gold paint, in the night we mourn together.
慟哭伝播する思いは心強くする
The wailing feelings that propagate strengthen my heart.
付いておいでよ
Follow me,
後ろに君がいるから
because you're behind me.
私は迷わない　光射す道へ
I won't hesitate, towards the path where the light shines.
無力だから仲間を求め
Because I'm powerless, I seek companions,
凍えるから火を灯して
because I'm freezing, I light a fire.
変化と共に進化してく
Evolving along with change,
この結末は誰も知らない
no one knows how this will end.
ミオしゃ
Miosha
君を信じる
I believe in you,
そう決めているから
because I've already decided to.
どんな異常も乗り越えられるよ
I can overcome any anomaly.
ミオしゃ
Miosha
月光　この闇に唯一凜と咲く花
Moonlight, the only flower blooming gallantly in this darkness.
畏怖なのか憧れなのか　向かい合う夜空
Is it awe or is it longing? The night sky we face together.
大地を駆け抜ける私と君が作り出す
Running across the earth, you and I create
この物語　単純な未来じゃない
this story, it's no simple future.
沸き立つ情熱　この声に乗せよう
The boiling passion, I'll put it into this voice.
空飛ぶ羽根なくても手を繋げられたから
Even without wings to fly, because we were able to hold hands,
この運命を選んだ
I chose this fate.
連呼する遠吠えは四島に響いて
The repeated howling echoes throughout the islands.
何度も何度もその絆を確かめ合った
Over and over again, we reaffirmed that bond.
瞬きを越え　駆け月　響く
Beyond the blink of an eye, the running moon resonates,
爪弾く道　金泥の群　共に嘆く夜
the plucked road, the group of gold paint, in the night we mourn together.
慟哭伝播する思いは心強くする
The wailing feelings that propagate strengthen my heart.
共に来いよ
Come with me,
隣に君がいるから
because you're right beside me.
私は迷わない　光射す道へ
I won't hesitate, towards the path where the light shines.
Listen to my howling...
狼が止まることはない
A wolf never stops.
みんなー！見てるー？
Everyone! Are you watching?
うちうち、うちだよー！
It's me, me!
大神ミオだよー！イエーイ！
It's Ookami Mio! Yay!
こんばんみおーん
Good evening-mio
こんばんみおーん！大神ミオです。
Good evening-mio! I'm Ookami Mio.
いやー、すごいね！ホロアースでのライブ、すごいみんな。
Wow, this is amazing! Everyone, this live in Holoearth is great.
いっぱい「ミオしゃ」とか「こんばんみお」とかやってくれてるから、
You're all sending so many "Miosha" and "Konbanmio" comments,
テンションも上がっちゃった！
that I've gotten really hyped up!
すごい嬉しい！ありがとう！
I'm so happy! Thank you!
いきなりね、あの、4曲連続でお送りしたわけなんですが、
We started off with four songs in a row, but...
まあちょっと、とりあえず他の3人にもね、登場してもらおうかな。
well, for now, let's have the other three join us.
あ、ミオしゃミオしゃ、ありがとう！はい、じゃあ行きましょう！
Ah, "Miosha, Miosha," thank you! Okay, let's go!
3人とも！フブキ、あやめ、みこち！
You three! Fubuki, Ayame, Mikochi!
ってコト！？
That's what it means!?
おいで、おいで！カモン、カモン！
Come on out, come on out!
わーい！
Yay!
フブちゃん
Fubu-chan
にゃっはろー！
Nya-hello!
きゃー！
Kyaa!
みこち
Mikochi
にゃっはろー
Nya-hello
なんだそのポーズ！
What is that pose!
こんばんみおーん！
Good evening-mio!
やったー！
We did it!
とまらない
Not stopping
さて、プロトライブ#2、ヤマトファンタジア、ついに始まっております！
Well then, Protolive #2, Yamato Phantasia, has finally begun!
かわいい
Cute
ねえ、ミオちゃんのハウリングめっちゃカッコよかった！
Hey, Mio-chan's Howling was so cool!
あやめのもめっちゃ可愛かったよ！
Ayame's was also really cute!
みこちもエリートだったぞ、にぇ！
Mikochi was also an elite, nye!
めっちゃよかった、よかった！
It was all so good, so good!
フブキもよかったね！
Fubuki's was also great, right!
全曲、ワーッ！オレンジですごい！
Every song was like "Whoa!" The orange was amazing!
最高！
The best!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
お疲れ様でしたー！
Good job, everyone!
良かったよねー！
That was great, wasn't it?
いや本当に、ステージまで全部和の世界だからさ。
Seriously, the whole stage and everything is in this traditional Japanese style.
そうそう。
Yeah, exactly.
なんか本当に漫画の世界にそのまま飛び込んできたって感じするよね。
It really feels like we've jumped straight into the world of a manga.
そうなんだよねー！ねー！
It really does! Right?!
で、今日のみやこも見た？
By the way, did you see the capital today?
見た見た！凄かったよね！
I did, I did! It was amazing!
見てきたけど凄かった。
I checked it out, and it was incredible.
あ、そうだ。ちょっとせっかくだし、
Oh, that's right. Since we're here,
このステージでみんなも遊んでみよう。
let's play around on this stage with everyone.
おー！
Oh!
遊べるの？
We can?
遊んでみようね。あの、みんなで、
Let's play. Well, I wanted to try...
あの、ウェーブをやってみたいなって。
...doing a wave jump with everyone.
みこ、思ってたんだよな。
I've been wanting to do it.
いけんのか？
Can we do it?
できんのかな？
I wonder if it'll work.
いや、あの、こっちの人たちから順番にこう、ジャンプを...
Yeah, like, everyone jumping in order starting from those people over there...
みこ、だいたい真ん中だぞ。
Miko, you're pretty much in the center.
あれ？
Oh?
本当だ。じゃあみんな凄い...
You're right. Then everyone...
みんな広がって！
Everyone, spread out!
みんな広がって！ちょっと離れて離れて。
Spread out, everyone! Step back a bit.
離れて離れて。はいはいはい、散れ散れ！
Back it up, back it up. Okay, scatter, scatter!
じゃあみここっちからうおーって行くから、みんなは「うふふー」ってやっててくださいね。
Okay, I'll go "Whooo!" from this side, so everyone else, go "Ufufu!"
オッケー。
Okay.
オッケー、じゃあ行くぞ、みんな！
Okay, here we go, everyone!
いくよー！せーの！
Ready? One, two...
うわあああああ！
Whoaaaaa!
うわああああああ！
Whoaaaaaaa!
おおー！行けてるー！
Oh! It's working!
ちょっと微妙な感じでした。
It was a bit messy.
ぴょんぴょんしてました。
Everyone was just hopping around.
ちょっとバラバラだったけど、でも追いかけてたね。
A bit uncoordinated, but they followed along.
まあまあ良かったんじゃない？
It was pretty good, wasn't it?
良かった良かった。
It was great, it was great.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
はい、というね、ちょっとお楽しみの中、残念なお知らせなんですけども...
Right, so while we're having fun, I have a bit of unfortunate news...
えー！？何、何？
Eh?! What is it?
ちょっとYouTube君がね... YouTube君がちょっとね...
Well, about YouTube... YouTube is...
あのですね、皆さん、大変お待たせいたしました中、見ていただきましたけれども、
So, everyone, thank you for waiting and watching until now, but...
なんとYouTubeの無料パーツが、ここまでとなります！
the free portion on YouTube ends here!
あらー！なのでね、是非この続きは、是非ね、あれですよね。
Oh no! So, please continue watching the rest over there.
はい、引き続き、Streaming+、SPWNの方でライブ配信しておりますので、
Yes, we're continuing the live stream on SPWN and Streaming+,
YouTubeを見ている方は動画の概要欄をチェックしてみてください！
so if you're on YouTube, please check the video description for details!
はーい！YouTubeのみんな、バイバーイ！
Okay! Everyone on YouTube, bye-bye!
バイバーイ！ありがとうございましたー！
Bye-bye! Thank you very much!
ヤマトファンタジア
Yamato Phantasia
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free portion has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!